{
    "subject": "Dina_Merrill",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Cliff_Robertson",
    "human_readable": "Dina Merrill is married to Cliff Robertson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886525273323059,
            "question": "Is Cliff Robertson married to Dina Merrill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9880508184432983,
            "question": "Is Cliff Robertson a spouse of Dina Merrill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9845656752586365,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Dina Merrill and Cliff Robertson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8944079875946045,
            "question": "Who is Dina Merrill married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8112502098083496,
            "question": "Can you tell me who is married to Dina Merrill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.763611376285553,
            "question": "Name the husband of Dina Merrill."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6938244104385376,
            "question": "What is the name of the man Dina Merrill is married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6183409690856934,
            "question": "What is the name of Dina Merrill's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6109536290168762,
            "question": "To whom is Dina Merrill connected in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5955907702445984,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Dina Merrill?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dina Merrill is married to Cliff Robertson.",
            "html": "yago_22844_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Dina Merrill connected in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_22844_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Dina Merrill's husband?",
            "html": "yago_22844_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the man Dina Merrill is married to?",
            "html": "yago_22844_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22844_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Dina Merrill is married to Cliff Robertson. The documents mention that they were married for 21 years, and provide specific dates of their wedding and divorce (December 22nd, 1966, and 1986). They also have a daughter named Heather together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Dina Merrill was married to Cliff Robertson for 21 years, and the marriage took place in 1966. This information supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}